hey guys I thought this was a fun
problem and I thought of a fun way to
demonstrate it let's focus right here
this X in the numerator can be broken
out into < TK x * squ root of x now
these two square root of x's match so
they can cancel each other out and now
we're stuck with just the square root of
x now let's focus on the square root of
square root of x the square root of a
square root of a number is the same
thing as the fourth root of a number now
let's focus on this right here we can
break this x into four fourth roots of x
and then one of these in the numerator
will cancel with this one in the
denominator that leaves us with of these
fourth root of x we can write these
three fourth roots of x as 4th root of x
cubed and now we have a square root of
the fourth root of x cubed that's the
same thing as the eth root of x cubed
and then looking at this x up here we
can break this down into 8 eth roots of
x and this eth root of x cubed this
three here is telling us there are three
of those now we can cancel one of these
with one of those another one with
another one and the third one with the
third one and we're left with five of
these eth roots of x or in other words
the eth root of x to the 5th now we have
the square root of the 8th root of x 5th
that's the same thing as the 16th root
of x 5th is the same thing as the 16th
root of x to the 5th and now to get rid
of this five we can take the fifth root
of both sides of the equation this fifth
root and this five are going to cancel
each other out and the fifth root of 32
is 2 and now to get X all by itself we
want to get rid of this 16th root we're
going to do both sides of the equation
to the 16th power this 16 exponent and
the 16th root will cancel each other out
so we just have X and 2 to the 16th
power is 2 multiplied out 16 times
that's going to be
65,536 and that is the answer to our
question let's put a box around it how
exciting